A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2005-2010
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Constituents, 2005-2009., Extent: 11.7 cu. ft. (26 boxes).
  - 2704076 - 2708523, 2007 December. (Box 025, Folder 5)
  - 2708527 - 2709952, 2007 December. (Box 025, Folder 6)
  - 2710075 - 2711028, 2007 December. (Box 026, Folder 1)
  - 2711036 - 2712148, 2007 December. (Box 026, Folder 2)
  - 2712197 - 2712799, 2007 December. (Box 026, Folder 3)
  - 2712034 - 2713190, 2008 January. (Box 026, Folder 4)
  - 2713207 - 2714441, 2008 January. (Box 026, Folder 5)
  - 2714452 - 2715259, 2008 January. (Box 026, Folder 6)
  - 2715327 - 2716312, 2008 January. (Box 026, Folder 7)
  - 2716359 - 2718009, 2008 January-February. (Box 027, Folder 1)
  - 2718093 - 2719345, 2008 January-February. (Box 027, Folder 2)
  - 2719363 - 2720837, 2008 February. (Box 027, Folder 3)
  - 2720846 - 2722113, 2008 February. (Box 027, Folder 4)
  - 2722114 - 2723344, 2008 February-March. (Box 027, Folder 5)
  - 2723371 - 2724694, 2008 March. (Box 027, Folder 6)
  - 2724782 - 2729868, 2008 March. (Box 028, Folder 1)
  - 2730127 - 2732023, 2008 March. (Box 028, Folder 2)
  - 2735095 - 2733251, 2008 March. (Box 028, Folder 3)
  - 2733253 - 2734915, 2008 April. (Box 028, Folder 4)
  - 2734919 - 2736194, 2008 April. (Box 028, Folder 5)
  - 2736201 - 2737762, 2008 April. (Box 028, Folder 6)
  - 2737763 - 2739820, 2008 April. (Box 029, Folder 1)
  - 2739839 - 2740911, 2008 April. (Box 029, Folder 2)
  - 2740916 - 2742212, 2008 May. (Box 029, Folder 3)
  - 2742230 - 2743213, 2008 May. (Box 029, Folder 4)
  - 2743290 - 2744152, 2008 May. (Box 029, Folder 5)
  - 2744168 - 2746206, 2008 May. (Box 029, Folder 6)
  - 2746210 - 2748045, 2008 June. (Box 030, Folder 1)
  - 2748046 - 2749219, 2008 June. (Box 030, Folder 2)
  - 2749247 - 2750058, 2008 June. (Box 030, Folder 3)
  - 2750066 - 2752113, 2008 June. (Box 030, Folder 4)
  - 2752129 - 2753290, 2008 June-July. (Box 030, Folder 5)
  - 2753295 - 2754737, 2008 June-July. (Box 030, Folder 6)
  - 2754802 - 2755819, 2008 July. (Box 030, Folder 7)
  - 2755865 - 2757370, 2008 July. (Box 031, Folder 1)
  - 2757396 - 2757692, 2008 July. (Box 031, Folder 2)
  - 2757729 - 2758971, 2008 July-August. (Box 031, Folder 3)
  - 2759005 - 2759866, 2008 July-August. (Box 031, Folder 4)
  - 2759871 - 2760896, 2008 August. (Box 031, Folder 5)
  - 2760905 - 2761868, 2008 August. (Box 031, Folder 6)
  - 2761911 - 2762803, 2008 August-September. (Box 032, Folder 1)
  - 2762818 - 2764032, 2008 September. (Box 032, Folder 2)
  - 2764109 - 2764709, 2008 September. (Box 032, Folder 3)
  - 2764722 - 2765373, 2008 September. (Box 032, Folder 4)
  - 2765374 - 2767806, 2008 September-October. (Box 032, Folder 5)
  - 2767822 - 2769220, 2008 September-October. (Box 032, Folder 6)
  - 2769299 - 2770083, 2008 September-October. (Box 032, Folder 7)
  - 2770126 - 2771748, 2008 September-October. (Box 033, Folder 1)
  - 2771759 - 2773410, 2008 October. (Box 033, Folder 2)
  - 2773413 - 2776401, 2008 October. (Box 033, Folder 3)
  - 2776409 - 2778012, 2008 October. (Box 033, Folder 4)
  - 2778045 - 2779076, 2008 October-November. (Box 033, Folder 5)
  - 2779129 - 2781042, 2008 October-November. (Box 033, Folder 6)
  - 2781054 - 2782643, 2008 November. (Box 034, Folder 1)
  - 2782714 - 2784021, 2008 November-December. (Box 034, Folder 2)
  - 2784023 - 2785683, 2008 November-December. (Box 034, Folder 3)
  - 2785719 - 2788215, 2008 December. (Box 034, Folder 4)
  - 2788223 - 2789346, 2008 December. (Box 034, Folder 5)
  - 2789359 - 2789982, 2008 December-2009 January. (Box 034, Folder 6)
  - 2780043 - 2791087, 2008 December-2009 January. (Box 034, Folder 7)
  - 2791102 - 2791780, 2009 January. (Box 035, Folder 1)
  - 2791802 - 2792322, 2009 January. (Box 035, Folder 2)
  - 2792333 - 2792996, 2009 January. (Box 035, Folder 3)
  - 2793014 - 2794105, 2009 January. (Box 035, Folder 4)
  - 2794156 - 2795258, 2009 January. (Box 035, Folder 5)
  - 2795292 - 2796117, 2009 February. (Box 035, Folder 6)
  - 2796118 - 2796876, 2009 February. (Box 035, Folder 7)
  - 2796880 - 2798329, 2009 February. (Box 036, Folder 1)
  - 2798354 - 2805104, 2009 February-March. (Box 036, Folder 2)
  - 2805108 - 2817613, 2009 March. (Box 036, Folder 3)
  - 2817723 - 2826640, 2009 April. (Box 036, Folder 4)
  - 2826670 - 2830550, 2009 April-May. (Box 036, Folder 5)
  - 2830638 - 2835992, 2009 May-June. (Box 036, Folder 6)
  - 2836001 - 2846391, 2009 June-July. (Box 037, Folder 1)
  - 2846672 - 2852881, 2008 August-September. (Box 037, Folder 2)
  - 2853007 - 2857134, 2008 September. (Box 037, Folder 3)
  - 2855078 - 2860265, 2009 September-October. (Box 037, Folder 4)
  - 2862374 - 2869356, 2009 November. (Box 037, Folder 5)
  - 2869364 - 2873103, 2009 December. (Box 037, Folder 6)
- Series III. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, 2005-2010., Extent: 6.75 cu. ft. (15 boxes).
  Contains incoming and outgoing correspondence and supporting documentation such as reports and memoranda related to specific topics, initiatives, organizations, and government agencies. Topics of note include board and commission appointments, FOIA requests, the First Lady's "For Keeps" initiative that focused on older foster children, the Governor's Healthcare Reform Commission, related work groups and public comment period, and the Virginia Tech incident response and Review Panel.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - AARP, 2006. (Box 038, Folder 1)
  - Access, 2007. (Box 038, Folder 2)
  - Agency accomplishments, 2006. (Box 038, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, U.S. Dept. of, 2006-2008. (Box 038, Folder 4)
  - Alignment project, 2006. (Box 038, Folder 5)
  - Anthem, 2007. (Box 038, Folder 6)
  - Appointments (Boards and Commissions), 2006. (Box 038, Folder 7)
  - Appointments (Boards and Commissions), 2007. (Box 038, Folder 8)
  - Appointments (Boards and Commissions), 2007. (Box 038, Folder 9)
  - Appointments (Boards and Commissions), 2007. (Box 038, Folder 10)
  - Appointments (Boards and Commissions), 2007. (Box 038, Folder 11)
  - Appointments (Boards and Commissions), 2008. (Box 038, Folder 12)
  - Aquaculture, 2006. (Box 038, Folder 13)
  - Arlington Community Action Program (ACAP) decertification, 2006. (Box 038, Folder 14)
  - Armour Home Care, 2006. (Box 039, Folder 1)
  - Assistive Technology Loan Fund Authority, 2005-2007. (Box 039, Folder 2)
  - Biosolids, 2006-2007. (Box 039, Folder 3)
  - Blind and Vision Imparied, Dept. for the (Commissioner), 2008. (Box 039, Folder 4)
  - Board Profiles, 2006. (Box 039, Folder 5)
  - Brain Injury, 2006-2007. (Box 039, Folder 6)
  - Brain Injury, 2006-2007. (Box 039, Folder 7)
  - Casey Foundation, 2007-2008. (Box 039, Folder 8)
  - Centers for Long Term Care Bankruptcy, 2007. (Box 039, Folder 9)
  - Certificate of Public Need, 2006. (Box 039, Folder 10)
  - Chamber of Commerce Visits, 2006. (Box 039, Folder 11)
  - Child Daycare Council Strategic Plan, 2006. (Box 039, Folder 12)
  - City of Suffolk, 2006. (Box 039, Folder 13)
  - Commonwealth Preparedness, 2008. (Box 039, Folder 14)
  - Community Services Board, 2006. (Box 039, Folder 15)
  - Comprehensive Services Act, 2006. (Box 039, Folder 16)
  - Comprehensive Services Act, 2006-2008. (Box 039, Folder 17)
  - Constituent, 2006. (Box 040, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Issues, 2006-2009. (Box 040, Folder 2)
  - Continuity of Government Plan, 2007. (Box 040, Folder 3)
  - Cosgrove, John A. (Delegate), 2006. (Box 040, Folder 4)
  - Cover Tennessee, undated. (Box 040, Folder 5)
  - Craig County (Governor's Letter), 2006. (Box 040, Folder 6)
  - Customer Service Report (Jayne Flowers), 2007. (Box 040, Folder 7)
  - Drug Court, 2006. (Box 040, Folder 8)
  - Early Childhood Initiative, 2007. (Box 040, Folder 9)
  - Ebbin, Adam (Delegate), 2006. (Box 040, Folder 10)
  - Electronic Health Records Task Force, 2005-2006. (Box 040, Folder 11)
  - Ethiopian Community Development Center, 2006-2007. (Box 040, Folder 12)
  - Evergreene v. DMAS and HHR, 2007. (Box 040, Folder 13)
  - Evergreene v. DMAS and HHR, 2007. (Box 040, Folder 14)
  - Executive Directive 2: Report of the Governor's Work Group on Rural Obstetrical Care, 2006. (Box 040, Folder 15)
  - Executive Orders, 2005. (Box 040, Folder 16)
  - Executive Orders, 2006-2007. (Box 040, Folder 17)
  - Family Drug Treatment Court, 2006. (Box 040, Folder 18)
  - Finance, 2006. (Box 040, Folder 19)
  - First Lady Event Requests, 2006-2007. (Box 040, Folder 20)
  - First Lady's "For Keeps" Initiative, 2007. (Box 040, Folder 21)
  - First Lady's "For Keeps" Initiative, 2007. (Box 041, Folder 1)
  - First Lady's Foster Teens Initiative, 2006. (Box 041, Folder 2)
  - FOIA Requests, 2006-2008. (Box 041, Folder 3)
  - FOIA Requests, 2009. (Box 041, Folder 4)
  - Food and Drug Administration, 2006. (Box 041, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly, 2006-2007. (Box 041, Folder 6)
  - Gifts Received, 2006-2009. (Box 041, Folder 7)
  - Gilbert, C. Todd (Delegate) - FOIA Request, 2007. (Box 041, Folder 8)
  - Gilbert, C. Todd (Delegate) - FOIA Request, 2007. (Box 041, Folder 9)
  - Gilbert, C. Todd (Delegate) - FOIA Request, 2007. (Box 041, Folder 10)
  - Gilbert, C. Todd (Delegate) - FOIA Request, 2007. (Box 042, Folder 1)
  - Gilbert, C. Todd (Delegate) - FOIA Request, 2007. (Box 042, Folder 2)
  - General, 2006. (Box 042, Folder 3)
  - General, 2006. (Box 042, Folder 4)
  - General, 2006. (Box 042, Folder 5)
  - General, 2006. (Box 042, Folder 6)
  - General, 2007. (Box 042, Folder 7)
  - General, 2007. (Box 042, Folder 8)
  - General, 2007. (Box 042, Folder 9)
  - General, 2008. (Box 043, Folder 1)
  - General, 2009. (Box 043, Folder 2)
  - Governor Kaine, 2006. (Box 043, Folder 3)
  - Governor Kaine, 2007-2008. (Box 043, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on the Future of Nursing, 2006. (Box 043, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Commission on Sexual Violence, 2006-2007. (Box 043, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Economic Development Strategic Plan, 2006. (Box 043, Folder 7)
  - Governor's FY 2008 Budget Reduction Plan - Detailed Report, 2007. (Box 043, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Health Reform Commission, 2006-2007. (Box 043, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Health Reform Commission Meetings and Public Hearings, 2007. (Box 043, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Health Reform Commission Work Groups, 2006-2007. (Box 043, Folder 11)
  - Governor's Health Reform Commission Work Groups, 2007. (Box 044, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Office for Substance Abuse Prevention, 2005-2006. (Box 044, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Office for Substance Abuse Prevention, 2007. (Box 044, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Strategic Plan, 2006. (Box 044, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Working Group on Early Childhood Initiatives, 2008. (Box 044, Folder 5)
  - Grants, 2006-2008. (Box 044, Folder 6)
  - HCA, 2006. (Box 044, Folder 7)
  - Health Partnership Act, undated. (Box 044, Folder 8)
  - Healthcare Reform, 2006. (Box 044, Folder 9)
  - Healthcare Reform (White Paper), 2006. (Box 044, Folder 10)
  - Healthcare Information Technology, 2005-2006. (Box 044, Folder 11)
  - Healthcare Information Technology, 2005-2006. (Box 044, Folder 12)
  - Healthcare Workforce Taskforce, 2006. (Box 045, Folder 1)
  - House Bill 1936 - Mandated Coverage of Treatment for Morbid Obesity, 2006. (Box 045, Folder 2)
  - Hurricane Evacuation and Sheltering Task Force, 2006. (Box 045, Folder 3)
  - Hurricane Evacuation and Sheltering Task Force, 2006. (Box 045, Folder 4)
  - Hurricane Evacuation and Sheltering Task Force, 2006-2007. (Box 045, Folder 5)
  - Hurricane Evacuation and Sheltering Task Force Report, 2006. (Box 045, Folder 6)
  - Information Technology Investment Board, 2005-2006. (Box 045, Folder 7)
  - Information Technology Investment Board - Recommended Technology Investment Projects (2006-2008 Biennium), 2006. (Box 045, Folder 8)
  - Information Technology Investment Board - Recommended Technology Investment Projects (2008-2010 Biennium), 2007. (Box 045, Folder 9)
  - Information Technology Investment Board - Recommended Technology Investment Projects (2008-2010 Biennium), 2008. (Box 045, Folder 10)
  - Interagency Civil Admissions Advisory Council, 2005-2006. (Box 046, Folder 1)
  - Joint Commission on Health Care, 2006. (Box 046, Folder 2)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 2006. (Box 046, Folder 3)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 2007. (Box 046, Folder 4)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 2007-2008. (Box 046, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Reception (2008), 2007. (Box 046, Folder 6)
  - Letters Signed by Secretary, 2006-2007. (Box 046, Folder 7)
  - Martinsville/Henry County Presentation, 2006. (Box 046, Folder 8)
  - Medicaid, 2006-2007. (Box 046, Folder 9)
  - Medicaid, 2006-2007. (Box 046, Folder 10)
  - Medicaid in Virginia, 2005. (Box 046, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda, 2005. (Box 047, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda, 2006. (Box 047, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda, 2007-2008. (Box 047, Folder 3)
  - Mental Retardation Waivers, 2006. (Box 047, Folder 4)
  - National Capital Region Exercise, 2008. (Box 047, Folder 5)
  - "No Wrong Door" Study, 2006. (Box 047, Folder 6)
  - North Carolina Health Risk Insurance Pool, 2007. (Box 047, Folder 7)
  - Nursing Education Programs in Virginia, 2010. (Box 047, Folder 8)
  - Nursing Education Programs in Virginia, 2010. (Box 047, Folder 9)
  - Pandemic Influenza Planning, 2007. (Box 047, Folder 10)
  - Perdue Pharma Oxycontin Settlement, 2007. (Box 047, Folder 11)
  - Performance Measures, 2006. (Box 047, Folder 12)
  - Performance Measures, 2006. (Box 048, Folder 1)
  - Planning and Budget Presentation, 2006. (Box 048, Folder 2)
  - Proclamations, 2006. (Box 048, Folder 3)
  - Program of All-Inclusive Care for the Elderly (PACE), 2006. (Box 048, Folder 4)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission, 2007. (Box 048, Folder 5)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (Dental/Oral Health), 2006-2007. (Box 048, Folder 6)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (Disability), 2007. (Box 048, Folder 7)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (General Workforce), 2007. (Box 048, Folder 8)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (Health Care Access Expansion), 2007. (Box 048, Folder 9)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (Infant Mortality Reduction), 2007. (Box 048, Folder 10)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (LTC Housing Access), 2007. (Box 048, Folder 11)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (LTC/DSP Workforce), 2007. (Box 048, Folder 12)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (LTC/DSP Workforce), 2007. (Box 048, Folder 13)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (Medicaid/FAMIS), 2007. (Box 049, Folder 1)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (Miscellaneous), 2007. (Box 049, Folder 2)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (Multi-point), 2007. (Box 049, Folder 3)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (Nursing), 2007. (Box 049, Folder 4)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (Obesity Prevention/Lunch Program), 2007. (Box 049, Folder 5)
  - Public Comment - Governor's Health Reform Commission (Tobacco Settlement), 2007. (Box 049, Folder 6)
  - Public Service Announcement - Early Intervention, 2007. (Box 049, Folder 7)
  - Regulatory Reform Health Care Working Group, 2006. (Box 049, Folder 8)
  - Regulatory Reform Health Care Working Group, 2008. (Box 049, Folder 9)
  - Regulatory Reform Health Care Working Group, 2008. (Box 049, Folder 10)
  - Report on the Feasibility of Transferring Adult Programs from the Dept. of Social Services to the Dept. for the Aging, 2007. (Box 049, Folder 11)
  - Riverside v. Eastern Virginia Health System Agency, 2006. (Box 049, Folder 12)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2006. (Box 049, Folder 13)
  - Selover Subpoena, 2006-2007. (Box 049, Folder 14)
  - Senate Finance Retreat, 2007. (Box 049, Folder 15)
  - Senators and Delegates, 2006. (Box 049, Folder 16)
  - Smart Beginnings, 2007. (Box 050, Folder 1)
  - Smoking/Executive Order 41, 2006-2008. (Box 050, Folder 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 2007. (Box 050, Folder 3)
  - State Executive Council, 2006. (Box 050, Folder 4)
  - State Plan Amendment - Plan for Medical Assistance for the Commonwealth, 2006. (Box 050, Folder 5)
  - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2006. (Box 050, Folder 6)
  - Superintendent of Schools, 2006. (Box 050, Folder 7)
  - SWAM Plans (FY 2010), 2009. (Box 050, Folder 8)
  - SWAM Plans (FY 2010), 2009. (Box 050, Folder 9)
  - SWAM Reports and Documentation, 2006-2008. (Box 050, Folder 10)
  - SWAM Reports and Documentation, 2008-2009. (Box 050, Folder 11)
  - Tappahannock LTC Center Bankruptcy, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 1)
  - Thank You Letters - Access to Care Work Group, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 2)
  - Thank You Letters - Governor's Advisory Council on the Future of Nursing, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 3)
  - Thank You Letters - Governor's Health Reform Commission, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 4)
  - Thank You Letters - Healthcare Workforce Task Force, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 5)
  - Thank You Letters - Long Term Care Work Group, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 6)
  - Thank You Letters - Quality, Transparency and Prevention Work Group, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 7)
  - Ticer, Patricia (Senator), 2006. (Box 051, Folder 8)
  - Tobacco Settlement Funding, 2006. (Box 051, Folder 9)
  - Transportation Memorandum of Understanding, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 10)
  - Truancy and Public Health Issues, undated. (Box 051, Folder 11)
  - University of Virginia, undated. (Box 051, Folder 12)
  - Urban Policy Taskforce, 2006. (Box 051, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council, 2006. (Box 051, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Executive Institute, 2006. (Box 051, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Office for Protection and Advocacy, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 16)
  - Virginia State Planning Grant, Phase II, 2006. (Box 051, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Tech Medical School and Research Institute, undated. (Box 051, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Tech Incident Review Panel, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Tech Response, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Tech Review Panel, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 21)
  - Virginia Tech Review Panel Report, 2007. (Box 051, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Workforce Council, 2006. (Box 052, Folder 1)
  - Webb, James (Senator), 2007. (Box 052, Folder 2)
  - Windsor Gardens v. Dept. of Social Services, 2008. (Box 052, Folder 3)
  - Work Alias, 2008-2010. (Box 052, Folder 4)
  - Workforce Development, 2006-2007. (Box 052, Folder 5)
  - Workforce Development, 2008. (Box 052, Folder 6)
  - Workforce Memorandum of Understanding, 2008. (Box 052, Folder 7)
  - Workforce Memorandum of Understanding, 2008. (Box 052, Folder 8)
  - Workforce Memorandum of Understanding, 2008. (Box 052, Folder 9)
  - Workforce (Miscellaneous), 2006. (Box 052, Folder 10)
  - Workforce (Miscellaneous), 2007. (Box 052, Folder 11)
  - Workforce (Miscellaneous), 2007-2008. (Box 052, Folder 12)
- Series IV. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary - Constituent Letters, DATES., Extent: 3.6 cu. ft. (8 boxes).
  Contains incoming and outgoing constituent correspondence that was filed as part of the correspondence of the Secretary. The filing structure of these letters is different from the structure of the letters found in Series II. and Series III., thus it was kept separate. The topics contained in the material are very similar to those found in Series II. Why these letters were filed seperately from the general constituent correspondence is unknown.
  Arranged alphabetically and then chronologically within.
  - A, 2006-2009. (Box 053, Folder 1)
  - B, 2006. (Box 053, Folder 2)
  - B, 2006. (Box 053, Folder 3)
  - B, 2007. (Box 053, Folder 4)
  - B, 2007. (Box 053, Folder 5)
  - B, 2007. (Box 053, Folder 6)
  - B, 2008. (Box 053, Folder 7)
  - B, 2009. (Box 053, Folder 8)
  - C, 2006. (Box 054, Folder 1)
  - C, 2007. (Box 054, Folder 2)
  - C, 2008. (Box 054, Folder 3)
  - C, 2009. (Box 054, Folder 4)
  - D, 2006. (Box 054, Folder 5)
  - D, 2007. (Box 054, Folder 6)
  - D, 2008-2009. (Box 054, Folder 7)
  - E, 2006. (Box 054, Folder 8)
  - E, 2007-2008. (Box 055, Folder 1)
  - E, 2009. (Box 055, Folder 2)
  - F, 2006. (Box 055, Folder 3)
  - F, 2007-2009. (Box 055, Folder 4)
  - G, 2006. (Box 055, Folder 5)
  - G, 2007-2009. (Box 055, Folder 6)
  - H, 2006. (Box 055, Folder 7)
  - H, 2006. (Box 055, Folder 8)
  - H, 2006. (Box 055, Folder 9)
  - H, 2007. (Box 055, Folder 10)
  - H, 2007. (Box 055, Folder 11)
  - H, 2008. (Box 056, Folder 1)
  - H, 2008. (Box 056, Folder 2)
  - H, 2009. (Box 056, Folder 3)
  - I, 2007; 2009. (Box 056, Folder 4)
  - J, 2006. (Box 056, Folder 5)
  - J, 2007-2009. (Box 056, Folder 6)
  - K, 2006-2007. (Box 056, Folder 7)
  - K, 2008. (Box 056, Folder 8)
  - K, 2008-2009. (Box 056, Folder 9)
  - L, 2006. (Box 056, Folder 10)
  - L, 2007. (Box 056, Folder 11)
  - L, 2008-2009. (Box 057, Folder 1)
  - M, 2006. (Box 057, Folder 2)
  - M, 2006. (Box 057, Folder 3)
  - M, 2006. (Box 057, Folder 4)
  - M, 2007. (Box 057, Folder 5)
  - M, 2008. (Box 057, Folder 6)
  - M, 2009. (Box 057, Folder 7)
  - N, 2006-2009. (Box 057, Folder 8)
  - O, 2006-2009. (Box 057, Folder 9)
  - P, 2006. (Box 057, Folder 10)
  - P, 2006-2007. (Box 058, Folder 1)
  - P, 2008-2009. (Box 058, Folder 2)
  - Q, 2006-2009. (Box 058, Folder 3)
  - R, 2006. (Box 058, Folder 4)
  - R, 2006. (Box 058, Folder 5)
  - R, 2007. (Box 058, Folder 6)
  - R, 2008. (Box 058, Folder 7)
  - R, 2009. (Box 058, Folder 8)
  - S, 2006. (Box 058, Folder 9)
  - S, 2006. (Box 058, Folder 10)
  - S, 2007. (Box 059, Folder 1)
  - S, 2008. (Box 059, Folder 2)
  - S, 2008-2009. (Box 059, Folder 3)
  - T, 2006. (Box 059, Folder 4)
  - T, 2007-2009. (Box 059, Folder 5)
  - U, 2006-2007. (Box 059, Folder 6)
  - V, 2006-2009. (Box 059, Folder 7)
  - W, 2006. (Box 059, Folder 8)
  - W, 2006. (Box 059, Folder 9)
  - W, 2007. (Box 060, Folder 1)
  - W, 2007. (Box 060, Folder 2)
  - W, 2008. (Box 060, Folder 3)
  - W, 2008. (Box 060, Folder 4)
  - W, 2009. (Box 060, Folder 5)
  - Y, 2006-2009. (Box 060, Folder 6)
  - Z, 2006-2009. (Box 060, Folder 7)
- Series V. Decision Memoranda and Briefs, 2006-2009., Extent: .675 cu. ft. (2 boxes).
  Contains decision brief packets submitted to Governor Kaine by agencies via the Secretary of Health and Human Resoures. The briefs include the request, recommendation, and approval signatures. Also included is background on the request, pertinent discussion, and financial impact statments. In some cases reference material and supporting documentation is included as well. Most of the files are grouped according to the agency requesting funds.
  Arranged alphabetically topic or agency.
  - Aging, Dept. for the, 2006-2007. (Box 061, Folder 1)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of, 2008-2009. (Box 061, Folder 2)
  - General, 2006. (Box 061, Folder 3)
  - General, 2007-2009. (Box 061, Folder 4)
  - Governor, 2006. (Box 061, Folder 5)
  - Health, Dept. of, 2006-2007. (Box 061, Folder 6)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 061, Folder 7)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 2007. (Box 061, Folder 8)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 2008. (Box 061, Folder 9)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 2009. (Box 062, Folder 1)
  - Social Services, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 062, Folder 2)
  - Social Services, Dept. of, 2007-2009. (Box 062, Folder 3)
- Series VI. Legislative Files, 2006-2009., Extent: 10.35 cu. ft. (24 boxes).